[
  {
    "question": "0＋0",
    "choices": [
      "9",
      "5",
      "0",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "0"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋1",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "7",
      "1",
      "5"
    ],
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋2",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "6",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋3",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "3",
      "1",
      "4"
    ],
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋4",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "4",
      "3",
      "1"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋5",
    "choices": [
      "9",
      "5",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋6",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "6",
      "5",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋7",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "10",
      "1",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋8",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "2",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋9",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "6",
      "7",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "0＋10",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "10",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋0",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "5",
      "10",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "1"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋1",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "10",
      "0",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋2",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "9",
      "3",
      "0"
    ],
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋3",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "7",
      "4",
      "0"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋4",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "1",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋5",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "1",
      "10",
      "0"
    ],
    "correct": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋6",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "8",
      "7",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋7",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "4",
      "1",
      "10"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋8",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "3",
      "9",
      "1"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "1＋9",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "9",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋0",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "7",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "2"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋1",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "8",
      "3",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋2",
    "choices": [
      "4",
      "0",
      "3",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋3",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "4",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋4",
    "choices": [
      "0",
      "6",
      "3",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋5",
    "choices": [
      "0",
      "2",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋6",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "4",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋7",
    "choices": [
      "0",
      "8",
      "9",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "2＋8",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "9",
      "1",
      "10"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "3＋0",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "5",
      "3",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "3"
  },
  {
    "question": "3＋1",
    "choices": [
      "0",
      "9",
      "4",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "3＋2",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "6",
      "5",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "3＋3",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "2",
      "6",
      "1"
    ],
    "correct": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "3＋4",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "7",
      "4"
    ],
    "correct": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "3＋5",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "0",
      "7",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "3＋6",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "2",
      "3",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "3＋7",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "3",
      "10",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "4＋0",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "4",
      "6",
      "10"
    ],
    "correct": "4"
  },
  {
    "question": "4＋1",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "5",
      "6",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "4＋2",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "6",
      "9",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "4＋3",
    "choices": [
      "1",
      "3",
      "7",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "4＋4",
    "choices": [
      "4",
      "8",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "4＋5",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "9",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "4＋6",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "5",
      "10",
      "1"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "5＋0",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "2",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": "5"
  },
  {
    "question": "5＋1",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "6",
      "3",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "5＋2",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "7",
      "9",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "5＋3",
    "choices": [
      "4",
      "10",
      "2",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "5＋4",
    "choices": [
      "6",
      "10",
      "2",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "5＋5",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "3",
      "1",
      "8"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "6＋0",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "2",
      "6",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": "6"
  },
  {
    "question": "6＋1",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "1",
      "5"
    ],
    "correct": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "6＋2",
    "choices": [
      "9",
      "5",
      "8",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "6＋3",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "3",
      "9",
      "4"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "6＋4",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "7",
      "8",
      "9"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "7＋0",
    "choices": [
      "5",
      "7",
      "3",
      "0"
    ],
    "correct": "7"
  },
  {
    "question": "7＋1",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "0",
      "2",
      "4"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "7＋2",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "9",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "7＋3",
    "choices": [
      "7",
      "2",
      "10",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "8＋0",
    "choices": [
      "8",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "8＋1",
    "choices": [
      "3",
      "9",
      "5",
      "1"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "8＋2",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "2",
      "5",
      "6"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  },
  {
    "question": "9＋0",
    "choices": [
      "2",
      "9",
      "1",
      "0"
    ],
    "correct": "9"
  },
  {
    "question": "9＋1",
    "choices": [
      "10",
      "6",
      "5",
      "7"
    ],
    "correct": "10"
  }
]